Okay. Now that you've got a list of all of
حسنًا. لقد حصلتم الآن على قائمة
their tables and
بكل الجداول
all of their columns, I want to give you a chance to mess around with them.
والأعمدة، وأريد أن أمنحكم فرصة للعبث بها.
On the next page, you can run whatever queries you like,
في الصفحة التالية، يمكنكم تشغيل أي استعلامات تريدونها،
using the zoo database.
باستخدام قاعدة بيانات "حديقة الحيوان"
You'll see a bunch of queries commented out in the editor.
سترون مجموعة من الاستعلامات تم التعليق عليها في المحرر.
Try uncommenting each of them and running it.
جربوا إلغاء تعليق كل منها وتشغيله.
Some of them use features you haven't seen yet.
يقوم بعضها باستخدام ميزات لم تروا حتى الآن.
Try to figure out what each of those features does.
حاولوا التعرف على أي من هذه الميزات صالح للعمل.
There's no right or wrong here, whatever you put in the query variable will
لا يوجد صواب أو خطأ هنا، فكل ما تضعونه في متغير "الاستعلام"
run against the database, when you press test run, and you'll see the results.
سيتم تشغيله في مقابل قاعدة البيانات، عند الضغط على "test run" وسترون النتائج.
Once you go on to the next page feel free to bookmark it, so
بمجرد الانتقال إلى الصفحة التالية فلا تترددوا في تحديدها كإشارة مرجعية،
you can come back later, any time you want to test out some SQL syntax.
لذلك يمكنكم الرجوع إليها لاحقًا، في أي وقت تريدون اختبار بعض بناء جملة SQL.
Once you're done use the submit button to move on.
بمجرد الانتهاء، يمكنكم استخدام الزر "submit" للمتابعة.